wpmoneyblog.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy — WordPress Money Blog

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy

in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use

of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, “How To Make Money Online Fast” will learn certain information about

you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology

called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”)

and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information

gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of

visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited

just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

 **What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique

identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer

for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically

designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser

if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser

only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not

the cookies sent to you by other sites.

 **IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the

Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network

to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web

server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data”

so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

 **Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content

of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We

provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ

in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

 **How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering

our business activities, providing customer service and making available other

items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

“How To Make Money Online Fast”  will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you

visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will

such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties

without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words,

when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection

of our legal rights.

A Special Note About Children

Children are not eligible to use our website and services and we ask that

minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If

you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and

guidance from your parents or guardians.

 **Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without

notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the

future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under

this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy

Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles

in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected

and maintained.

 _ **Contact**_

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our

web site, please contact us.

 _ **curtis.vineet@gmail.com**_
